

ANDREY PAVLYCHEV

UI ARTIST AND ANIMATOR

ADDRESS: Samui, Thailand PHONE: +66 (096) 236-33-10

E-MAIL: drawn.loves.you@gmail.com

WEB: https://dribbble.com/drawn, http://be.net/drawn

PROFILE

As a graphic designer and animator, I have gained valuable experience designing arts for a number of various games for about 10 years. Being a creative, reliable, hard-working and challenging designer, I can work well in a collaborative team environment or individually. My career goals are to continue to learn and grow as an artist while keeping on improving my creativity, knowledge and skills.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE ARTIST

Samui, Thailand | January 2015 - Present

Development of graphic game content for individual clients. Mobile apps.

UI DESIGNER

KRIVORUKOFF LLP | Samui, Thailand | March 2014 — January 2015

Mobile games. Both redesigning current interfaces and developing new ones; creating interface animation samples for the developers; building user interfaces in Unity3D (NGUI Framework); icon design.

Projects: Adventure Era, Epic Squad.

ARTIST AND 2D-ANIMATOR

CRAZYBIT LLC | Moscow, Russia | July 2010 - March 2014

Browser, Social and Mobile games. Complete cycle development of game graphics, starting from designing and making UI assets up to creating logos and App Icons; design of various buildings and sprites for city-builders and "Clash of Clans"- like games; characters and in-game items animation.

Projects: Lost Island, Lost Chapters, Experiment, Hellout, Soldiers of Fortune, S.O.S, Metro City, Sinners, BOOM!

FLASH DESIGNER

IT-TERRITORY/MAIL.RU | Moscow, Russia | December 2009 — July 2010

Browser and Social games. Development of graphic game content; design of interfaces; animation.

Projects: TimeZero, Juggernaut, Legends: Legacy of the Dragons, In the Hood, Cosmics, Troetsarstvie.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

TIMEZERO LLC | Moscow, Russia | September 2007 — December 2009

Browser and Social games. Graphics development for the company game projects; interfaces and icons design; creating in-game items; characters animation. Development of promotional content; corporate identity and merchandise design.

Projects: TimeZero, Destiny Online, BUGS, Evil Tale, Crouching Panda Hidden Moose, Funny War, Dragons, Pyramid.

DESIGNER

ERA LLC | Moscow, Russia | October 2006 — August 2007

Company web-site design, content management. Design of packaging and promotional materials.

EDUCATION

Saransk, Russia | 2002 - 2008

Area Studies Specialist, Mordovia State University

Saransk, Russia | 1996 — 2001

Pictural Art Department, Saransk State Art School #4

SKILLS

UI design, Icon design, Game items design, Logo Design, Character and UI animation (2D), Flash banners (with no Action Script).

SOFTWARE

Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Flash, Sketch app, Unity3D (NGUI framework). JIRA, Redmine, Trello, GitHub. OSX